Guide to the Fredericka Martin Papers ALBA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X. 2020 Accretion, 1930-2019; 1.5 linear feet in 2 manuscript boxes and 2 half manuscript boxes
  - Personal Correspondence -- Ben Berenberg, 1961-1981 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Family, 1974-1981 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Paul Nelson, 1943-1946 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence -- The Silver Fleece, 1974-1981 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence -- Margaret Shedd, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Research Trip on American Medical Bureau in Spanish Civil War, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Spanish Civil War, 1946-1982 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - "Spanish Diary," James Neugass, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Spanish Newspaper Clippings, 2019 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - United American Spanish Aid Committee, American Rescue Ship Mission, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - University of Alaska-Fairbanks Library, circa 1972 (Box 43, Folder 10)